configserver.com 2019-09-14

# Way to the Web Privacy Policy

### Introduction

Your privacy and data security is important to Way to the Web Limited. The purpose of this policy is to explain how we collect and use any personal information when you use our [Website](https://www.configserver.com/), and any subdomains. In addition to this Privacy Policy, your use of the services is governed by our [ConfigServer Ordering Terms and Conditions](https://configserver.com/orderinfo.html), [ConfigServer Services Terms and Conditions](https://configserver.com/terms.html) and individual License Terms and Conditions (see each products license terms from their product page).

### Contents

  * How we collect information about you
  * What information we collect and how long it is kept
  * How we use your personal information
  * The legal basis for our use of your information
  * When we may share your personal information
  * Where the information is stored and data security
  * Your rights of access, correction, and deletion
  * How we use cookies
  * How to contact us
  * Links to other sites

### How we collect information about you

Way to the Web Limited collects information from you when you browse the website, including our forum, store and helpdesk, and when you provide it directly by filling out forms on the website such as placing an order for products or services or creating an account on the helpdesk.

### What information we collect and how long it is kept

When you visit our website we collect information such as your IP address, your ISP, which pages you view on the Website, the time and duration of visits, the external page from which you came to our website, and information about your web browser. This information is usually retained for four weeks.

When you create an account on our [store](https://store.configserver.com/) we collect information provided by you including name, postal address, email address, company name and contact, and IP address. When you place an order we collect information including products ordered, payment methods used, and IP address. No credit card numbers or other specific payment information is collected. This data is kept indefinitely but for a minimum of 7 years for business accounting and tax purposes.

When you create an account on our [helpdesk](https://support.configserver.com/) we collect information you provide for your profile account including name, email address, country, organisation, and avatar. When you use our helpdesk we collect information including ticket contents, attachments, custom field data, activity log, email log and failed logins. This information is kept indefinitely.

When you use our [forum](https://forum.configserver.com/) we collect information you provide such as your name if you provide it, username, email address, IP address, contents of posts and private messages including IP addresses. This information is kept indefinitely.

When you send us an email the information we collect will include the contents of the email and the IP addresses of servers through which the email has been routed. Emails are kept indefinitely.

### How we use your personal information

Website data is used to evaluate and improve our website, and for security and fraud prevention.

Information collected via our store is used to verify, process and fulfill orders, carry out the services you have ordered, and provide customer support.

Information collected within our helpdesk is used to carry out the services you have ordered and provide technical support.

Information collected via our forum is used for security reasons and to allow you to utilise the forum to communicate with other users of our software.

We do not process any personal information for marketing purposes, nor do we sell or rent any of the information you have provided to third parties.

### The legal basis for our use of your information

Website information is collected under the legal basis of Way to the Web Limited's legitimate interests of performing tasks related to security and fraud prevention, and maintaining and improving our Website.

The legal basis for the collection of information on users of our forum is your consent and the legitimate interests of the company related to security.

The collection of information in the store and helpdesk is under the legal basis of our contract with you as well as our legitimate interests for security and fraud prevention.

### When we may share your personal information

Your information may be shared with our server providers, accountant, payment processing providers, software providers (in the event of technical support requirements), and any agency we are required by law to provide the information to or in the context of investigation of suspected fraud or violations of our Terms of Service or License Terms. 

We do not share any of your information with third party marketing or advertising companies.

### Where the information is stored and data security

Your information is stored on servers controlled by Way to the Web Limited and provided by our chosen server providers, as well as on computers at the offices of Way to the Web Limited. Only employees of Way to the Web Limited and its data processors have access to this information. Industry standard practices are used to protect this data from accidental loss, misuse, unauthorised disclosure, alteration or destruction. These measures include firewalls, transmission encryption, password protection, security scanning software and other practices to protect the transmission and storage of your information.

### Your rights of access, correction, and deletion

If you live in the European Union, you have the right under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) to request a copy of the information we hold about you. You may ask us to correct or remove information that you think is inaccurate. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal data or wish to have some or all of your data deleted, email us at support@waytotheweb.com. We may be required by law to retain some of your data, for example information relating to past orders in our Store.

### How we use cookies

Way to the Web Limited uses the following types of cookies:

Strictly necessary: These cookies enable our Website to function correctly and deliver the services and products you have requested.

Performance & Functionality: These cookies are used to enhance the performance and functionality of the Website but are non-essential to their use (for example, these cookies remember your preferences on the Website).

By using the Website, you accept the use of these Strictly Necessary and Performance & Functionality cookies in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

You may deactivate cookies in your web browser, or reject the creation of a cookie depending on your personal preferences. If you do so then our Website functionality may be compromised and certain services may not be available.

### How to contact us

You can contact us regarding this Privacy Policy and your personal information by email at support@waytotheweb.com Please see our [Contact Page](https://configserver.com/contact.html) for further contact details.

### Links to other sites

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by Way to the Web Limited on this Website. This Website may contain links to other sites, and Way to the Web Limited cannot be held responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. If you leave our site to visit another site that may collect personally identifiable information, you should read the privacy statement on that website.
